Guide to the Washington Area Music Association records, 1984-2016 MS2331
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Area Music Association records
1984-2016
1994-2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Area Music Association
MS2331
23.5 Linear Feet
This collection consists of approximately 1,300 CDs representing the work of musicians local to the Washington Area, including Maryland and Northern Virginia. Additionally, the collection holds financial records, marketing material, recordings, photographs, meeting minutes, fundraising records, production records, correspondence, articles, memos, meeting minutes, press releases, early organizational records, and other official papers that document the work of the Washington Area Music Association from 1984 to 2016. The collection was compiled by the non-profit Washington Area Music Association (WAMA) as part of their mission to promote the work of local artists.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of approximately 1,300 compact discs (CDs) and other audio recording formats such as DVDs, pocket CD-Rs, VHS tapes and casette tapes, featuring the music of a wide variety of artists local to the Washington D.C. and Northern Virginia/Maryland area. Additionally, the collection features the files, information, and other records of WAMA while the organization was functional. The materials range in date from 1984 to 2016; the bulk of the material dates to between 1994 and 2001. This collection of recordings and paper records were originally compiled by the Washington Area Music Association (WAMA), a non-profit organization of music industry professionals dedicated to promoting and celebrating the work of Washington Area Musicians.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Washingon Area Music Association (WAMA) is a non-profit organization of music industry professionals dedicated to promoting and celebrating the work of musicians from the Washington and Northern Virginia/Maryland area. Founded in 1985, the organization consists of a board of directors and an advisory board composed of musicians, managers, recording engineers, record industry professionals, lawyers, and others with an active role in the Washington area music community. The organization is run entirely through the effort of volunteers. WAMA sponsors the annual "Wammies" award show, which honors local musicians for achievement in a wide variety of music genre, reflecting the diversity of the DC music scene. WAMA also hosts charitable events and provides services to DC musicians, such as a music calendar, musician directory, and seminars on topics relating to the music business.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research.
Collection Organization
Arranged into 8 series: Recordings of Washington area musicians on CD format, Recordings of Washington area musicians on non-CD formats, Governance, Productions, Audio/Visual materials, Artist/Band Promotional materials, Published materials and Photographs and posters.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Washington Area Music Association, 2014 August 27, (2014.029) and 2018 May 17, (2018.020).
Custodial History
Accession 2018.020 was temporarily held by GW Music Professor Christopher Lornell before being transfered to the Special Collections Research Center in 2018.
Musicians; Music; Music -- Washington (D.C.); Musicians -- Washington (D.C.); Washington Area Music Association
- Recordings of Washington area musicians on non-CD formats, 1995-2002; Series 2
  Arrangement
  Series arranged alphabetically by artist
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of a small number of recordings of musicians local to the Washington Area, including Maryland and Northern Virginia, in alternative formats (one pocket CD-R, two cassette tapes, two DVDS and one VHS tape).
  - Artists B-R, 1995-2002; Series 2; 7 item(s) (Box 13)
- Recordings of Washington area musicians on CD format, 1984-2012; 1994-2001; Series 1
  This series consists of approximately 1,190 CDs representing the work of musicians local to the Washington Area, including Maryland and Northern Virginia. Many of the artists and specific albums represented here have been recognized by the Washington Area Music Association at their annual "Wammies" award ceremony. Among the diverse genres represented are Bluegrass, Blues, Country, Electronic, Jazz, Latin, Punk Rock, Reggae, Rock, World, and more.
  This series is subdivided into 29 subseries, arranged alphabetically by genre and ending with Undetermined Genre: Bluegrass; Blues; Celtic; Children's; Classical; Country; Easying Listening; Electronic; Folk; Folk Rock; Funk/Funk Rock; Gospel/Religious; Hip Hop; Holiday; Jazz; Latin; Metal; Musical Soundtrack; New Age; Pop; Punk/Post-Punk; Rap; Reggae; Rhythm & Blues/Soul; Rock; Spoken Word; Swing/Big Band; World; Subseries 29: Undetermined Genre
  - Bluegrass, 1996-2012; Series 1 Subseries 1
    Arrangement Note
    CDs arranged alphabetically by artist within series.
    - Artists A-R, 1996-2012; Series 1 Subseries 1; 14 item(s) (Box 1)
  - Blues, 1984-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Artists A-S, 1992-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2; 75 item(s) (Box 1)
    - Artists S-W, 1984-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2; 16 item(s) (Box 2)
  - Celtic, 1992-2002; Series 1 Subseries 3
    CDs arranged alphabetically by artist within series.]
    - Artists C-M, 1992-2002; Series 1 Subseries 3; 16 item(s) (Box 2)
  - Children's, 1998-2009; Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Artists B-R, 1998-2009; Series 1 Subseries 4; 9 item(s) (Box 2)
  - Classical, 1996-2009; Series 1 Subseries 5
    - Artists B-P, 1996-2009; Series 1 Subseries 5; 8 item(s) (Box 2)
  - Country, 1996-2009; Series 1 Subseries 6
    - Artists B-W, 1996-2009; Series 1 Subseries 6; 27 item(s) (Box 2)
  - Easy Listening, 1994-2009; Series 1 Subseries 7
    - Artists B-T, 1994-2009; Series 1 Subseries 7; 15 item(s) (Box 2)
    - Artists T-V, 1995-1998; Series 1 Subseries 7; 5 item(s) (Box 3)
  - Electronic, 1999-2009; Series 1 Subseries 8
    - Artists A-W, 1999-2009; Series 1 Subseries 8; 18 item(s) (Box 3)
  - Folk, 1993-2011; Series 1 Subseries 9
    - Artists A-P, 1982-2011; Series 1 Subseries 9; 67 item(s) (Box 3)
    - Artists P-W, 1993-2006; Series 1 Subseries 9; 24 item(s) (Box 4)
  - Folk Rock, 1996-2011; Series 1 Subseries 10
    - Artists A-M, 1996-2011; Series 1 Subseries 10; 16 item(s) (Box 4)
  - Funk/Funk Rock, 1995-2009; Series 1 Subseries 11
    - Artists B-Y, 1995-2009; Series 1 Subseries 11; 26 item(s) (Box 4)
  - Gospel/Religious, 1997-1999; Series 1 Subseries 12
    - Artists C-T, 1997-1999; Series 1 Subseries 12; 6 item(s) (Box 4)
  - Hip Hop, 1997-2003; Series 1 Subseries 13
    - Artists A-W, 1997-2003; Series 1 Subseries 13; 17 item(s) (Box 4)
  - Holiday, 1992-2011; Series 1 Subseries 14
    - Artists C-R, 1992-2011; Series 1 Subseries 14; 5 item(s) (Box 4)
    - Artists S-T, 1995-2000; Series 1 Subseries 14; 4 item(s) (Box 5)
  - Jazz, 1990-2010; Series 1 Subseries 15
    - Artists A-P, 1990-2009; Series 1 Subseries 15 (Box 5)
    - Artists R-V, 1992-2010; Series 1 Subseries 15; 39 item(s) (Box 6)
  - Latin, 1993-2006; Series 1 Subseries 16
    - Artists B-Y, 1993-2006; Series 1 Subseries 16; 26 item(s) (Box 6)
  - Metal, 1990-2001; Series 1 Subseries 17
    - Artists D-S, 1990-2001; Series 1 Subseries 17; 10 item(s) (Box 6)
  - Musical Soundtrack, 1994-2003; Series 1 Subseries 18
    - Artists J-W, 1994-2003; Series 1 Subseries 18; 3 item(s) (Box 6)
  - New Age, 1995-2000; Series 1 Subseries 19
    - Artists A-R, 1995-2000; Series 1 Subseries 19; 10 item(s) (Box 6)
  - Pop, 1990-2010; Series 1 Subseries 20
    - Artists A, 1999-2001; Series 1 Subseries 20; 5 item(s) (Box 6)
    - Artists B-T, 1990-2006; Series 1 Subseries 20; 93 item(s) (Box 7)
    - Artists T, 1992-2010; Series 1 Subseries 20; 3 item(s) (Box 8)
  - Punk/Post-Punk, 1993-2002; Series 1 Subseries 21
    - Artists B-U, 1993-2002; Series 1 Subseries 21; 46 item(s) (Box 8)
  - Rap, 1991-2006; Series 1 Subseries 22
    - Artists A-T, 1991-2006; Series 1 Subseries 22; 13 item(s) (Box 8)
    - Rhythm & Blues/Soul, 1991-2006; Series 1 Subseries 24
      - Artists A-D, 1995-2006; Series 1 Subseries 24; 6 item(s) (Box 8)
      - Artists H-W, 1991-2005; Series 1 Subseries 24; 23 item(s) (Box 9)
  - Reggae, 1989-2002; Series 1 Subseries 23
    - Artists A-S, 1989-2002; Series 1 Subseries 23; 19 item(s) (Box 8)
  - Rock, 1991-2011; Series 1 Subseries 25
    - Artists A-E, 1996-2011; Series 1 Subseries 25; 71 item(s) (Box 9)
    - Artists E-O, 1991-2008; Series 1 Subseries 25; 90 item(s) (Box 10)
    - Artists P-Z, 1993-2010; Series 1 Subseries 25; 85 item(s) (Box 11)
  - Spoken Word, 2005-2007; Series 1 Subseries 26
    - Artists G, 2005-2007; Series 1 Subseries 26; 2 item(s) (Box 11)
  - Swing/Big Band, 1995-2010; Series 1 Subseries 27
    - Artists B-K, 1995-2010; Series 1 Subseries 27; 9 item(s) (Box 11)
    - Artists M-T, 1999-2010; Series 1 Subseries 27; 14 item(s) (Box 12)
  - World, 1991-2005; Series 1 Subseries 28
    - Artists A-X, 1991-2005; Series 1 Subseries 28; 14 item(s) (Box 12)
  - Undetermined Genre, 1991-2011; Series 1 Subseries 29
    - Artists A-M, 1993-2002; Series 1 Subseries 29; 76 item(s) (Box 12)
    - Artists M-Z, 1991-2011; Series 1 Subseries 29; 62 item(s) (Box 13)
- Governance, 1984-2014; Series 3; 3.75 Linear Feet
  This series consists of the papers and processes from when the WAMA foundation was a working organization, documenting the bodies and tools of governance.
  - Administrative Records, 1984-2004; Series 3 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains the administrative records of WAMA from its inception in 1984 to 2004. The materials include office records, correspondence, marketing material, production records, publications, and other early organizational records.
    This subseries is organized chronollogically.
    - WAMA, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Music Month, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - WAMA, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Press releases, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Special Events, 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - WAMA city paper, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Membership, 1987-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - WAMA ethics, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Kid Creole, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bias Recording Company, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - WAMA- misc, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - WALA Conference, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Resume, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Niagra, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Christmas Party, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - CD AP, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Freedom Plaza, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Minority Cacuas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - WAMA- misc, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - WAMA, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Workshop, 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondance, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - WAMA files- spring, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Voting and Nominating, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Careers in Music, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Rap it up, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - DC CD, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Awards, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Falls Church Event, 1994-2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - C.T.J., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - DC CD Contracts, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Event Script, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Video Project, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Strathmore Series, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - DOO WOP & DC, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - What is WAMA (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Contracts for Musicians (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Incorporation (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Misc. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Board of Director Meetings, 1985-2014; Series 3 Subseries 2
    This subseries documents records relating to the Board of Directors, include annual reports, meeting agendas and papers, meeting transcripts, and meeting minutes, Word-for-word transcription of many of the Board of Director's meetings, as well as collections of Board materials and meeting agendas reflect broadly the priorities of the WAMA foundation.
    - Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Board Meeting, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Board Meeting, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Board Meeting, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Board Meeting, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records, 1986-1994; Series 3 Subseries 3
    The Finance Records document well the financial activities and concerns of the WAMA foundation, the condition of the program's finances throughout part its history, and the various changes in procedures and policies concerning financial matters.
    This subseries is organized chronologically.
    - WAMA tax file, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Legal, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - CD Requests, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Membership records, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - WAMA Special Productions, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Bank/Credit Card/ Summary Reports, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Budgets, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - WAMA tax files, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Wammies Accounting, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Checks/Receipts, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Payables, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Financial Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Commission on the Arts, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Last Resort, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - WAMA finances, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Niagra, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Checks/Receipts, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Alliance, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Finances, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Finances, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Finances, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Productions, 1985-2011; Series 4; 2.75 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged in to two subseries: Wammies and Crosstown Jam.
  It docments the records for WAMA's annual Crosstown Jam, a citywide music festival, and fundraising event, and the Wammies, a local music awards program.
  - Wammies, 1985-2011; Series 4 Subseries 1
    The subseries includes flyers, posters, postcards, press releases, programs, and correspondence. The material relates to the productions undertaken by WAMA to produce its annual Wammies music awards.
    - Wammies- settlement, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Wammies, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Wammies- cya file, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Wammies sponsorship, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wammies, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Wammies #3, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Wammies 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Wammies- 90, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Wammies Ballots, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Wammies, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Wammies, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Wammies, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Wammies- 96, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Wammies, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Wammies, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Wammies, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Wammies, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Wammies, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Wammies, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Wammies, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 2005 Wammies (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 22nd Wammies, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Wammies, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Wammies, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Wammies, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Wammies, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Crosstown Jam, 1986-2004; Series 4 Subseries 2
    The subseries includes flyers, posters, postcards, press releases, programs, and correspondence. The material relates to the productions undertaken by WAMA to produce its annual Crosstown Jams music festival.
    - Crosstown, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Crosstown, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Crosstown, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Crosstown, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Crosstown, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Crosstown, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Crosstown, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Crosstown, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Crosstown, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Crosstown, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - C.T. Bills, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Crosstown, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Crosstown, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Crosstown, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Crosstown, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Crosstown, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Nominations, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Crosstown, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Crosstown, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Crosstown, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Audio Visual materials, 1985-2013; Series 5; 4 Linear Feet
  This series is comprised of VHS cassettes, CDs, and two vinyl records.
  The series is grouped by audio/visual type. The VHS cassettes are organized first in chronological order, then the CDs are arranged next alphabetically, and lastly the two vinyl records.
  - Wammies- 1st and 2nd VHS, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Wammies VHS, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Wammies VHS, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Wammies- State VHS, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - WAMA VHS, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - WAMA VHS, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - WAMA VHS, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Wammies VHS (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - WAMA CDs, 1986-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - WAMA CDs, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - WAMA CDs, 2004-2007 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - WAMA CDs, 2009-2011 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - WAMA CDs, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - CDs- A (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - CDs- A-B (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - CDs- B (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - CDs- B-C (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - CDs- C (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - CDs- C-D (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - CDs- D (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - CDs- D-E (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - CDs- D (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - CDs- F-G (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - CDs- G (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - CDs- H (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - CDs- H (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - CDs- H-J (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - CDs- J (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - CDs- K-L (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - CDs- L-M (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - CDs- M (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - CDs- M (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - CDs- M-N (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - CDs- N-O (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - CDs- O-R (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - CDs- R-S (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - CDs- S (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - CDs- S (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - CDs- S-T (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - CDs- T-U (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - CDs- U-W (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - CDs- W-Y (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Vinyl Records (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Artist/Band Promotional materials, 1985-2009; Series 6; 2.5 Linear Feet
  This series is comprised of folders, pampletes, business cards, photographs, and other content sent to WAMA from rising artists and bands in the surrounding DC metropolitan area.
  This series is organized alphabetically.
  - About Time (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Al and the Kidd (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Alligator, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Allard, Terri, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Carl, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Annie R and Rapture, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Atomics, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Baaba Seth (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Back to Back, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Barrett, Randy (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Betty, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Bicycle Thieves, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Big Black Nuns, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Big Jesse Yawn (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Bjorklund, Terri (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - BlueBlack (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - The Boneheads (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Blue Juke Joint (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Blues Works (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Bogart, Deanne, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Born Jamaicans!, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Bowers, Bryan (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Chuck (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Bobby Radcliff (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Burge, Todd, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Byrd, Charlie, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Caglo, Mac, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Capricorn (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Cassel, Frank, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Casselberry Dupree, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Cassidy, Eva, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - The Cicadas (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Cathy and Marcy, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Chorne, Rich (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Circle of Friends (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Clements, Vassar (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - The Clovers (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Clutch (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Cotter, Mike, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Cubic Feet, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - D., Lena, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Dahl,Richard (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Danforth, Ricky (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Dark angels (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - DC ide (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - DC Talk, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Disappear Fear (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Deun, Boud (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Delvin, Bob, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - DJ Kool (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Doug Segree Band, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Douglas, Ernie, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Droogz (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dukes, Becky (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Dumm Dumms (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Earth Eighteen, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Eaton, John (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Eddie from Ohio (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Edwards, Archie, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Englishman Maccabee, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Esmirelda (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Fields, Elysian, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Fink, Cathy (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Flemming, Marianne (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Francis, Cleve, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Foo Fighters (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - The Four of Us (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Gatton, Danny, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ghost of Tom, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Griffith, Grace, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Gill, Johnny (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Gil, Tony (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Girlie Action, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Girls Against Boys, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Glad (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Goffin, Gerry (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - GUM! (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Grainger (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - GWAR (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Bill (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Heyman, Richard (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Hodge, Bob (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Honeypole, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Horn, Shirely (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Howard, Greg, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Husik, Lida (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - The Huge, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - In Flux, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - IID Etreme (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Imani and First Prayer (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Intersound (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Iona, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Ivery, Michael, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Jane Doe, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Janes and Julia (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Jawbox, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Jay, Doug, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jesus Freak, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Jireh (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - The Johnson Mountain Boys, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Jonathon Fire Eater, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Kage, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Keating, Vicky, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Keene, Tommy (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - The Kingdom of Leisure (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy, Pete (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Kennelly, Cletus, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 13)